{
  "questions": [
    {
      "number": 1,
      "question": "Who is the current captain of the Indian cricket team?",
      "option1": "Sachin Tendulkar",
      "option2": "Sunil Chhetri",
      "option3": "Virat Kohli",
      "option4": "Rohit Shrama",
      "correctAnswer": "Virat Kohli"
    },
    {
      "number": 2,
      "question": "Who is the current captain of the Indian football team?",
      "option1": "Baichung Bhutia",
      "option2": "Sunil Chhetri",
      "option3": "Sandesh Jhingan",
      "option4": "Rohit Shrama",
      "correctAnswer": "Sunil Chhetri"
    },
    {
      "number": 3,
      "question": "When did India win the first cricket world cup?",
      "option1": "1996",
      "option2": "1983",
      "option3": "2011",
      "option4": "2019",
      "correctAnswer": "1983"
    },
    {
      "number": 4,
      "question": "Which tennis player has the best record on clay courts?",
      "option1": "Rafael Nadal",
      "option2": "Novak Djokovic",
      "option3": "Roger Federer",
      "option4": "Andy Murray",
      "correctAnswer": "Rafael Nadal"
    },
    {
      "number": 5,
      "question": "Which one of the following football clubs is the oldest",
      "option1": "Real Madrid",
      "option2": "FC Barcelona",
      "option3": "Mohun Bagan",
      "option4": "Liverpool FC",
      "correctAnswer": "Mohun Bagan"
    },
    {
      "number": 6,
      "question": "Ryder cup is related to which sports?",
      "option1": "Polo",
      "option2": "Golf",
      "option3": "Badminton",
      "option4": "Tennis",
      "correctAnswer": "Golf"
    },
    {
      "number": 7,
      "question": "Pen Holder grip is used in which of the following sports?",
      "option1": "Polo",
      "option2": "Golf",
      "option3": "Badminton",
      "option4": "Table Tennis",
      "correctAnswer": "Table Tennis"
    },
    {
      "number": 8,
      "question": "When was the last time the Olympic salute was used?",
      "option1": "1956",
      "option2": "1948",
      "option3": "1974",
      "option4": "1924",
      "correctAnswer": "1948"
    },
    {
      "number": 9,
      "question": "With which sport is Dutee Chand associated?",
      "option1": "Sprint 100m",
      "option2": "Long Jump",
      "option3": "High Jump",
      "option4": "Discus Throw",
      "correctAnswer": "Sprint 100m"
    },
    {
      "number": 10,
      "question": "Who had founded the International Olympic Committee in 1894?",
      "option1": "Jacques Rogge",
      "option2": "Demetrios Vikelas",
      "option3": "Pierre de Coubertin",
      "option4": "Henry Kissinger",
      "correctAnswer": "Pierre de Coubertin"
    }
  ]
}
